# PAIGE TETZLAFF

## FULL STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER

## CONTACT









#### EDUCATION

## SOFTWARE ENGINEERING CERTIFICATE

**FLATIRON SCHOOL** 

2022-2023

### BACHELOR OF ARTS MANDARIN CHINESE

THE OHIO STATE UNIVERSITY

2017-2020

#### **ASSOCIATE OF ARTS**

COLUMBUS STATE
COMMUNITY COLLEGE

2015-2017

#### SKILLS

Object Oriented Programming

Javascript

React

Ruby on Rails

Python

Web Design

Debugging

Leadership

Teamwork

Mentorship

#### SUMMARY

Experienced in Ruby on Rails and JavaScript-based programming and a background in customer service. Highly motivated and adaptable professional with a degree in Mandarin Chinese. Strong background in retail sales and management. Developed excellent communication and leadership skills. Now transitioning to a career in software engineering.

#### PROJECTS

## CLASSICS LIST





A full-stack web application that enables book enthusiasts to share reviews, engage with other users, and manage their profiles for seamless interaction within the community.

- Constructed a React frontend and Ruby on Rails backend
- Implemented a user profile management system for easy access, editing, and deletion of user reviews
- Incorporated dynamic user ratings to update overall book ratings in real-time
- Ensured secure user authentication and authorization with Bcrypt integration

#### WANDER





A full-stack web application that allows users to browse, share, and engage with various travel experiences, providing valuable insights for future travelers and enhancing trip planning.

- Developed a React frontend and Ruby on Rails backend
- Created an intuitive user interface for seamless browsing, commenting, sharing, and reviewing of travel experiences
- Enabled users to like and comment on unique travel experiences to foster engagement and interaction

#### EXPERIENCE

### SALES LEAD/ KEY HOLDER

Buff City Soap

#### June 2022 - September 2023

- Consistently achieved highest sales in store
- Supervised and changed associates in sales, customer service/complaint resolution, and production
- Maintained personal in-house production quotas
- Nurtured and maintained a loyal customer base

#### VISUAL SPECIALIST/ CUSTOMER SALES LEAD

Pandora Jewelry

#### October 2019 - March 2020

- Employed strong visual design skills to create appealing displays and efficiently managed store alterations during campaign changes
- Demonstrated proficiency in group sales and fostering customer relationships
- Progressed to managing and leading teams effectively